<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DoSS Toolkit</title>
    <link>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DoSS Toolkit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.dosstoolkit.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Overview We all know that R is a critical part of statistics these days, but it can have a steep learning curve and be intimidating to get started with. The Department of Statistical Sciences (DoSS) toolkit is a free series of open source online modules written by undergraduates, that their fellow students and the public can use to learn the essentials of R.
 Contributors  Annie Collins is an undergraduate student in the Department of Mathematics specializing in applied mathematics and statistics with a minor in history and philosophy of science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessment</title>
      <link>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/assessment/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons</title>
      <link>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/lessons/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modules</title>
      <link>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dosstoolkit.com/modules/</guid>
      <description>How to use this resource You use this resource by running R code! This may sound intimidating if you’ve never used R before, so we’ve made a video that walks through what you need to do.
 Get started by going to R Studio Cloud - https://rstudio.cloud - and creating an account. When you’ve signed up, start a new project, and copy-paste the code below to install packages. (If you already have R and R Studio working on your local computer then you don’t have to use R Studio Cloud, you can install the packages on your local machine instead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
